https://kcacr.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how the Kent County Association of Change Ringers (KCACR) uses and protects any information that you give them when you use this website.
The KCACR is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
The KCACR may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 16th May 2018.
Information we collect (mailing list members only)
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to enable you to be a member of the mailing list, and in particular for the following reasons:
To send you news and/or information relating to ringing within the Association area, nationally or internationally
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you and can request the update or removal of all or some of this information.  If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email gensec@kcacr.org.uk.
Sign up to the KCACR Mailing List
First Name
Last Name
Email address:
District
Ashford
Canterbury
Lewisham
Maidstone
Rochester
Tonbridge
None/Outside Kent
Leave this field empty if you're human: Upcoming Events
Follow KCACR on Twitter
Tweets by @kcacrofficial
Latest News from the Central Council
Further development of Coronavirus guidance – the Path AheadLast Friday lunchtime, I was notified by my daughter’s school that one person in her year group had tested positive for Coronavirus and the entire year group was being sent home to self-isolate for 10 days. One of the first things she did on getting home was to say that she wouldn’t be able to ... Read moreFurther development of Coronavirus guidance – the Path Ahead [...]Shake my hand and I’ll show you the ropes“Shake my hand and I’ll show you the ropes” A biography of George Pipe by John Loveless NOW AVAILABLE FOR PRE-ORDER (release date Friday 6th November) £18.50 (includes UK postage and packaging*) Hardback, 240 pages. Available from shop.ringingworld.co.uk Preorders open Friday 9th October Orders open Friday 6th November Price £18.50 From a Suffolk family with ... Read moreShake my hand and I’ll show you the ropes [...]President’s Blog #19The days have probably gone when ringers chose their universities based on the ringing opportunities available. Many of my contemporaries will admit that ringing was a factor in their own choices, but those were different times, times when the “Desmond” (a.k.a. the “Ringer’s Degree”) was almost, but not quite, a badge of honour. For young ... Read morePresident’s Blog #19 [...]How can we improve Public Relations in ringing and in our towers?An online talk by Vicki Chapman (Wednesday 30th September, 7pm (UK)) Join Vicki Chapman, PR Rep for the Central Council, as she leads us in a discussion about public relations in ringing. Vicki will focus both on ringing PR in general and for towers. This is the first in a series of talks offered jointly ... Read moreHow can we improve Public Relations in ringing and in our towers? [...]President’s Blog #18I wouldn’t be surprised if no ringer below the age of 20 is reading this. I would be pleased if they were, but I am realistic enough to know that our print and social media does not hit a youth audience. This point came up this week because Julia Cater asked whether the distribution of ... Read morePresident’s Blog #18 [...]
Latest KCACR Performances
1260 Minor (2m)Rung on Friday, 9 October 2020 at Tonbridge (2A Cranford Road), Kent. [...]Call ChangesRung on Sunday, 4 October 2020 at Ashford (St Mary the Virgin), Kent. [...]1272 Plain Bob MinimusRung on Sunday, 4 October 2020 at Tunstall (7 Bradley Drive), Kent. [...]1272 Plain Bob MinimusRung on Sunday, 4 October 2020 at Tunstall (7 Bradley Drive), Kent. [...]5160 Spliced Royal (2m)Rung on Saturday, 3 October 2020 at Bromley (10 Wharton Road), Kent. [...]
Links to local websites
Ash-by-Wrotham
Beckenham
Biggin Hill
Brasted
Canterbury Cathedral
Canterbury, St. Stephen
Deal
Great Chart, Hothfield, Kennington, Little Chart & Sevington
This site uses cookies:
Find out more.Okay, thank you
